

KEERTHANA UNNI

SYMBIOSIS CENTRE FOR MEDIA AND COMMUNICATION

PERSONAL DOSSIER

I am an 18 year old curious being who loves challenges and learning from them. I strongly believe the world is in need of fresh ideas and that the youth are highly capable of doing far more brilliant things than what the world can possibily imagine.

WORK EXPERIENCE CIRCLE BLINK

-Memeber of AV team for Azaad Awaaz festival September 2019

RUSH SPORTS FEST

-Member of AV team January 2020

ROTARY CLUB OF VIMAN NAGAR

-Member of AV team of host club to cover District Confrence January 2020

POSITIONS HELD

- -Head girl 2018-19
- -Deputy head girl 2017-18

ACHIEVEMENTS

- -National level athlete 2015-18
- -Finalist at Gems Education and Singularity University
- -English Elocution Champion 2015–18
- -Best film poster at The Children's International Film Festival 2018

SKILLS

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- -Audio Visual (Photography and Videography)
- -Content and creative writing
- -Social media marketing

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- -Evaluation skills
- -Ability to communicate effectively
- -Positive outlook
- -Creative thinking
- -Problem solving skills
- -Event management
- -Critical thinking
- -Leadership skills
- -Public speaking

EDUCATION

SYMBIOSIS CENTRE FOR MEDIA AND COMMUNICATION Bachelor's Degree in Communication

- Bachelor of Arts Mass Communication
- First Year

GEMS OUR OWN ENGLISH HIGH SCHOOL, DUBAI CBSE Humanities Stream (Class XI and Class XII)

- Class of 2019
- Percentage 88.8%

GEMS OUR OWN ENGLISH HIGH SCHOOL, DUBAI CBSE (Class IX AND X)

- Class of 2017
- CGPA 9.4/10

CONTACT DETAILS

Phone No: +917356684476

Email: keerthanaunni2001@gmail.com